[bus rumbling]
[radio DJ] It's been a huge year
for the box office, hasn't it?
The first half was dominated
by Kwak Kyung-taek's Friend.
"You go to Hawaii."
And now, in the latter half of the year,
My Sassy Girl is taking theaters by storm.
Gyeon-woo,
today's first song
is Shin Seung-hun's "I Believe."
[upbeat music playing]
[cheering]
[music ends]
[children coughing]
[child 1] That guy is doing it again.
[child 2] Is there something
wrong with him?
[coughing]
-[child 3 laughs]
-[children coughing]
[coughing continues]
What was your name again?
Dance Machine,
DM,
Hwang Hyun-woo, officially.
-You 18?
-Nineteen.
You're so young looking.
Are you…
on a special diet?
It could be because
I grew up eating pork rinds.
[sighs]
Do you want me to sing for you now?
I'm already aware
of your singing abilities.
Just by speaking with you,
-I've determined your vocal range.
-I want to be a singer…
and a dancer.
Being a singer isn't anything special.
Anyone can do it
if they meet a competent producer.
Give me a year to train you properly,
and then you'll be a pop star.
What is it?
Don't want to?
Oh, no, no. It's not that I don't want to…
[sighs]
I just don't feel
like I really deserve it.
All right, I'll do it!
'Cause this is my time!
We're on the same page,
even though we just met each other.
Exciting, isn't it?
[both chuckle]
Whoa!
If I'm being honest,
I wasn't holding out a lot of hope.
But how great to rehearse
in such a beautiful building.
-I'll give it everything I have, and--
-What are you doing? That's not it.
SAMWOO ENTERTAINMENT AGENCY
Okay, Well, the inside looks better
than the outside does.
It's clean and seems
pretty decent, actually.
-I'll do my best to succeed and--
-Where do you think you're going?
It's down here.
YONGGU RECORDS
Your bandmates are waiting
right behind that door.
On the road to success,
courage is required.
Go ahead.
Open the door.
[band member] Gonna pound in the sound!
Baby!
Yo!
Ha!
Gonna pound in the sound!
Woo!
Gu Sang-gu!
Let's go!
-I think you did it.
-Yo! Hey!
It's pounded all the way in,
you can stop now.
-Where's Do-mi?
-[toilet flushes]
[Sang-gu sighs]
Who's he?
Say hello, guys.
This is your new band mate.
Uh…
Dance Machine, DM,
Hwang Hyun-woo.
This is Do-mi and Sang-gu.
Do-mi sings, Sang-gu raps.
And as for you,
you'll sing and dance. A double threat.
Huh? B-But we've already got a vocalist.
He'll do sub vocals.
But, Mr. Park, we're an old-school,
rap-centric, hip-hop duet.
That was the old you.
From now on, you're a trio!
A co-ed trio!
-A co-ed trio?
-But-But you promised me…
That means we would
have to split the profit three ways.
Why do you keep staring at me?
You wanna black eye?
Well, damn.
You promised me an old-school,
rap-centric, hip-hop duet.
And now you're trashing all our plans
because you wanna make us dance!
You weren't trying to rap that, were you?
Your debut song is out,
let's give it a listen.
[singsongy] Everybody gather 'round.
[sighs]
"LOVE IS" DEMO
["Love Is" playing]
This place is dangerous.
You like it?
It's good, huh?
What did you pay for it?
It's not hip-hop at all.
Now that we have a song,
we just need to hire someone
to work out the dance moves.
[Hyun-woo] The choreo?
Leave that to me.
1ST ALBUM PROMOTION
Guys, make sure you don't freeze up
-when they turn the cameras on you.
-[scoffs]
And, whatever you do,
don't be freaked out by the audience.
You talk way too much. Are you scared?
The pastor at my old church
would get super scared before the service,
so he'd tell himself…
"Everyone here except me
is a worthless piece of shit."
-Then he wasn't scared anymore.
-Worthless piece of shit.
[scoff] A pastor who swears
at his congregation?
Nice church you went to.
-Oh! Hyung, I think it's starting to work.
-[mutters]
-Oh, yeah? Cool.
-Yeah.
Everyone but me is a piece of shit.
-Yo, everybody's just a piece of shit.
-[muttering]
Yo! Everybody's just a piece of shit!
-Hey, hey, hey, hey. Just quiet down.
-[yelps] Quiet down!
-Let's go. Come on.
-[breathes heavily]
-Let's go!
-Wait, wait, wait, wait.
-Dancing Hyun-woo!
-[gasps]
-[distant cheering]
-Singing Do-mi!
Rapping Sang-gu!
[all] Triangle!
-Let's go!
-Yo!
[MC] …the trio set to conquer
the music industry
with a super powerful dance extravaganza.
Here's Triangle's debut performance
of "Love Is."
"LOVE IS" BY TRIANGLE
TOP 10 MUSIC
♪ Yo ♪
[cheering]
"LOVE IS" IS RISING FAST
ROOKIE TRIO
TAKES THE MUSIC SCENE BY STORM
[cheering continues]
♪ Everybody! ♪
♪ Everybody, body! ♪
SWEEPS MUSIC SCENE
TEEN FAN BASE FORMS ON DEBUT
♪ Uh, uh, come on, now! ♪
♪ Come on now! Let me hear you say ♪
♪ What's up? Say Tri, Tri, Triangle ♪
♪ Say T-T-Triangle ♪
[grunts]
[in Korean] ♪ Meeting you
Was the greatest stroke of luck ♪
♪ When I look back
On all my days ♪
♪ The more I get to know you
The more scared I get ♪
♪ How much of it
Did you ever really mean? ♪
♪ No way, what if you do this?
What if you do that? ♪
♪ I bet that's what you're thinking
It's so obvious ♪
♪ Will you just stop and answer me? ♪
♪ It's not time yet, I mean right now ♪
♪ You shouldn't do that
You shouldn't do this ♪
-♪ Why is it so complicated, baby ♪
♪ Love is, why is it, why is it
So hard? ♪
♪ Even though every day, every day
You still make me laugh and cry ♪
♪ That it will last forever
That it will go on ♪
♪ Promise me, my love ♪
[in English] ♪ Oh, my love ♪
[grunts]
♪ All my people, say, ho! ♪
♪ Put your hands up in the air, yo! ♪
-♪ Say, hey, ho! ♪
-♪ Hey, ho! ♪
[in Korean] ♪ What is love? Love is ♪
♪ What even is love? Love is ♪
[in English]
♪ One, two, three, let's go! ♪
[cheering]
DANCING MACHINE HYUN-WOO
BYEON DO-MI ROCKS
ONLY YOU, HWANG HYUN-WOO
-[cheering, screaming]
-[fan 1] Hyun-woo, over here!
[fan 2] We love you, Hyun-woo!
2ND ALBUM PROMOTION
[Do-mi chuckles]
How come our balloons
are three different colors?
-Because the primary colors of light are…
-Hi!
-[cheering]
-…red, green, and blue.
[reporter] I'm here with the group
that burst onto the scene
like a comet last year,
whose second album has made them
a contender for number one this year.
One, two, three.
[all] Hello!
We are!
[all] Triangle!
I heard the leader of the group,
Hwang Hyun-woo, wrote and composed
-every single song on this album.
-[Hyun-woo] Ah.
-[Do-mi gasps]
-Uh,
the main thing that helped me
with my creative struggle
was thinking of all our fans out there.
[reporter chuckles] Can we call you
a singer-songwriter from now on? [laughs]
TOP 10 MUSIC, UP FOR #1
TRIANGLE
-[laughs]
-[reporter] Oh, and Do-mi,
-I heard that you in particular…
-Yeah.
-…received some vocal training.
-[gasps]
Ah, yes, that's true.
I always look for ways to improve myself.
There's no such thing
as a day off for this girl.
-[reporter] Wow, what remarkable passion.
-[chuckles]
[reporter laughing]
-Yo, check it out. Peace.
-[reporter] Pew.
Nice. Okay,
that was Triangle,
our first interview of the day.
-[chuckles]
-What about…
-Uh, uh. Mmm. [chuckling]
-Oh.
-[Hyun-woo] Tri… angle!
-[Do-mi, Sang-gu] Angle!
-Thank you.
-Thank you!
Our next interview
is another number one contender,
like Triangle.
The man who's commonly known
as the Prince of Ballads,
-Choi Seong-gon.
-Hmm.
You just broke the record
for being the number two spot the longest.
How about saying a little something
to your fans?
Coming in at number two for 38 weeks,
it's your knight in shining armor,
Choi Seong-gon,
standing by your side, as always.
I want to say that my fans
are my sole reason for being.
-And I want to reveal that I'm actually…
-Uh-huh.
-…a big fan of that group over there.
-[reporter] Oh!
Triangle,
-love you.
-[reporter] Woo!
-[Do-mi squeal]
-[Seong-gon] Love.
Ugh, 38 weeks at number two.
And that damn Tricycle or whatever
is already a contender?
I've been working my ass off
to get to number one.
[staff] Seong-gon,
please get ready for the stage.
-Thanks.
-Love you.
Man, it was hard keeping up
that fake friendly act. [sighs]
So you wrote all our songs, did you?
Hyung, you can't even read music.
Mr. Park told me to say that,
since I'm the group leader.
What was I supposed to do?
Okay, then what am I? A lackey?
Yeah, I guess you are.
You're an idiot!
How dare you!
Take it outside.
-That cheesy bastard's starting his song.
-[MC] Number two on the charts
for a whopping 38 weeks,
here's the tenacious Prince of Ballads,
Choi Seong-gon,
making another run at the number one spot
with "I Like You."
[in Korean] ♪ I like you ♪
[backup singers vocalize]
♪ I like you ♪
♪ I like you because you're pretty ♪
[backup singers] ♪ Because you're pretty ♪
♪ I like you ♪
♪ I like you because you're kind ♪
[backup singers] ♪ Because you're kind ♪
♪ I like you ♪
♪ I like you so much I could die ♪
We like you back!
-♪ You like me too ♪
-I like you too!
♪ We like each other ♪
♪ Ooh, ah, ooh-ah ♪
[in English] The truth is that
I just…
like you the way you are.
-[cheering, screaming]
-Number one!
♪ Shout it out
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
-♪ Shout it out, shout it out ♪
LOVE YOU, TRIANGLE
THE BEST IN THE UNIVERSE
[MC] Now, all that's left is to reveal
the number one song for this week.
-Dancing Machine Hwang Hyun-woo!
-Combining album sales,
-broadcast score, and live ARS votes…
-[audience] ♪ I like you ♪
…the number one song
on Top 10 Music this week is…
Will it be Triangle or Choi Seong-gon?
Triangle, Choi Seong-gon.
Choi Seong-gon, Triangle!
Now, after tallying the final scores
for the second week of March
on Top 10 Music…
Spot number two…
-goes to Choi Seong-gon…
-Yeah!
…with Triangle coming in at number one!
-[audience cheering, screaming]
-[MC 2] Congratulations!
[MC 1] Congratulations!
Yeah!
[laughs]
-[grunts]
-[Hyun-woo whimpers]
[Do-mi gasps]
[MC 1] Why don't you say a few words
to our audience.
I never thought that
the first song I ever wrote
would hit number one like that.
To our RGB Army,
I love you!
#1 "SHOUT IT OUT" BY TRIANGLE
[Do-mi] Triangle will continue
to do our best
and to work as hard as we can
in order to make sure our music
keeps on improving. Thanks!
[MC 1] We'll leave you now
with an encore performance
by our number one winner, Triangle.
-See you next week. Everyone, goodbye!
-Goodbye!
[audience cheering]
[Seong-gon sighs] They're having a party
just because they hit number one once?
TOP TEN MUSIC NO. 1
[clicks tongue] I don't get it.
How is it that such a crappy song
is number one? [clicks tongue]
-I'm going home now.
-Oh!
Gon, Gon, Gon!
Don't go yet.
Everyone from the network is here.
The CEO wants you
to schmooze a little, okay?
-I'm not doing that.
-Hey, hey, hey.
The network director is thinking
of making you number one on the next show.
It'll be ten months at number two
if you don't make it next week.
At least I'll still have my pride.
-Mr. Producer.
-Who is that?
-Is that a friend of yours?
-I'm looking for the producer…
Uh, was it the producer,
or the network director…
Mr. Network Director.
-[gasp]
-[Seong-gon] Oh, sorry.
-Mr. Producer.
-[guest laughing]
-Just wondering…
-Hey.
-…if the producer's in there--
-Just get in. Come on, move it.
-Uh, what? Um…
-[sighs]
-[door closes]
-[guest coughing]
Here.
-Thanks.
-[guests laughing]
[chuckles]
I heard the network director
and the producer were here, so I…
He'll be here soon.
Just have a smoke while you wait.
Hey, don't do that.
What's the matter with you?
[guest 2] Give me some of that.
[Seong-gon] Huh?
[distorted, singing in Korean]
♪ I like you ♪
[in English] You're number one in my eyes.
You're the real number one.
Number two for 39 weeks?
-You're the best.
-Number two, Choi Seong-gon.
-You're a prince.
-I'm telling you, you're the best.
-The Prince of Ballads.
-Number two for 39 weeks?
[distorted, singing in Korean]
♪ I like you so much I could die ♪
-[chattering]
-[dance music playing]
[in English] So, did you talk to him?
About us getting paid?
Our dough. Huh?
The money. The dough he owes.
Dough, dough, dough, where's our dough?
Why are you coming at me about it?
Well, you're the leader, aren't you?
Hyun-woo.
Ah, g-goodness. C-Congratulations.
Congrats.
Oh, that was just insane, man!
-Oh. [chuckling]
-Seriously, totally insane!
-You were amazing. [chuckles]
-Oh, thanks.
Who are you?
I, uh… I'm with Megaton o-over there.
I'm Na Tae-poong.
Are you really in Megaton?
Yeah, we met a few times already.
Excuse me. Uh, someone pooped
on the bathroom floor,
-could you clean it up?
-It wasn't me who did it.
Hey, Sang-gu, he's not actually a waiter.
He's in Megaton…
-Jang-poong!
-[chuckles]
Oh, my mistake, sorry.
-Tae-poong.
-Oh.
-Na Tae-poong.
-Yeah.
Jang-poong sounds better.
You should use that instead.
What a great idea.
-It is.
-[Tae-poong laughs]
Ah.
-[grunts, chuckles]
-[sighs]
-[chuckles]
-Seriously,
-congratulations. You were amazing.
-Thanks.
Seriously, totally amazing. [chuckles]
Okay.
Oh, oh. Hello, Mr. Park.
I'm from Megaton, Na--
[grunts, chuckles]
Hey kiddos! Why are you
just sitting around?
-How come you're not partying?
-Uh…
Hi, Mr. Park, uh…
Remember that thing
I brought up a while ago?
Your money, right?
I mean, we still haven't gotten paid
for last year's album promos.
You know how it is.
It takes time to work these things out.
So, uh… [sigh]
It's the nature
of this business, actually.
-It's not that we haven't processed…
-[mouthing words]
…your payments, they're just deferred.
In accounting terms, you could say
your money's on a vacation right now.
Hold on a sec. I'm getting a call.
[grunts]
[sighs]
See that?
That's how I handle things as the leader.
Well, if we don't get paid soon,
you'll be number one
on my kill list. Got it?
[snoring]
[groaning]
[groans]
[exclaims]
Hey, why aren't you guys
answering your phones?
I've got some bad news.
-What is it?
-[groans]
[both grunt]
[manager] It's all over the papers and TV.
They can't talk about us like that.
CELEBRITIES' TRASHY
HEDONISTIC PARTY?
We just had a few drinks
and kicked back, is all.
Ugh, that's so wrong!
[grunts]
Damn it. Seriously?
What's the deal? Is that guy crazy?
This guy?
Why the hell would he strip
at someone else's party?
-Is it true that you used drugs?
-What lewd acts did you engage in?
I didn't-- No, it wasn't me.
Are you denying both the drug use
and lewd acts?
If you did use drugs,
who did you use them with?
Was this your first time?
If not, when did you start using?
RELIABLE POLICE
A SAFE COUNTRY
[reporter] Just moments ago, singer Choi
Seong-gon was spotted being brought in
for questioning by local police.
Last night, Choi attended a party…
Did you guys do drugs at the party?
I bet you did.
You look like you did. I can tell just by
looking at you. Man, you did, didn't you?
He took something. I knew it.
Shut up, dude, I don't even take aspirin.
I knew that corny poser was bad news,
-could tell by the way he combs his hair.
-[footsteps running]
Oh, hyung, did you get it sorted out?
"PLAGIARISM CONTROVERSY"
The singing group Triangle is currently
embroiled in a plagiarism scandal.
Huh?
The title track of their second album,
written and composed by their leader,
Hwang Hyun-woo, is suspected of
plagiarizing a popular Bulgarian song.
Let's take a listen.
[Hyun-woo] ♪ Shout it out
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Shout it out
♪ Shout it out ♪
ORIGINAL SONG - BULGARIA
[Bulgarian singers] ♪ Shout it out
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh… ♪
[scoffs]
-They're not similar at all. Are they?
-[reporter] Which one is Triangle's song,
and which one
is the popular Bulgarian song?
The first one was ours, wasn't it?
No, ours was the second song.
Or maybe not.
I can't tell which one was us!
…their agency, Yonggu Records,
has not yet released a statement.
[phone ringing]
It's such a beautiful day.
The sky looked just like this
on the day you and I first met.
It's an extraordinary thing
to witness someone making their exit
at the right time.
[Hyun-woo] Hey, you can't leave!
You have to clean up this mess first!
Adios.
Hello, are you there?
[gasps]
[sighs] Okay.
Don't take this the wrong way.
It's not necessarily
because of this, okay?
Lately I've been feeling
really limited in Triangle
and got this great offer the other day,
so I think I'm just gonna go.
[chuckles]
Was the offer from Mr. Hong's company?
You think I could get in there too?
I don't think so.
-I can't believe you guys!
-[knocking on door]
[shushes]
Who is it?
[knocks on door]
-Mr. Hwang Hyun-woo!
-[reporters clamoring]
[reporter 1] Why did you choose
to plagiarize a Bulgarian artist?
[reporter 2]
Aren't you gonna make a statement?
Please give us a moment of your time.
Hiding won't solve anything!
[clamoring continues]
[breathing heavily]
Ah, this can't be real!
Yeah!
It's a nightmare.
You have to force yourself to wake up now.
[alarm blaring]
PRESENT DAY
[groaning]
-[blaring stops]
-[sighs]
[sighs]
[Hyun-woo]
I never wanted to show my boyfriend
the less-than-perfect side of myself,
but then a real challenge came my way.
It was when I was meeting his parents
for the first time.
Somehow,
I ended up sitting on my boyfriend's
father's lap at dinner.
[laughing]
HE THINKS IT'S FUNNY
CAN'T STAND HIS LAUGH
WHO'S THIS GUY? JUST SOME DUDE?
[humming]
Excuse me.
You know I was a huge fan of Triangle.
[chuckles]
I had a feeling that was the case.
It was so impressive when the four of you
would dance in sync back then.
[chuckles]
We were a trio.
-Ah…
-Mm-hmm.
A trio.
[sighs]
You guys were the best boy band
out there, dude.
It was a co-ed group.
[sighs] Kiss ass.
-Sorry?
-Uh, I said "guest."
I'm a regular on this show,
and you're our special ki…
guest today.
[both chuckling]
[chuckles]
Guest.
Thanks for all your hard work up to now.
[laughs]
Oh, is the show format changing?
-Wait, it's not being canceled is it?
-[chuckles]
Oh, no way. Not with our amazing ratings.
So it's just me who's getting let go?
This whole thing is completely my fault.
But, Mr. Oh,
this is my main job.
It's the only show I do.
What about your cable show?
You know that I got cut from that
over six months ago.
You and I don't know each other that well,
so it's not the kind of thing
I'd be aware of.
We could get to know each other better,
if you want.
We work well together, huh?
-I'll pass.
-At least tell me the reason.
What did I do wrong? I want to know.
You've been out of the industry
for so long now,
people don't know who you are.
Listeners are constantly asking about
why we always have this rando on the show.
Really? I'm the rando?
You should've gone on a variety show.
I mean, Na Tae-poong from Megaton blew up
because of the variety show he was on.
He's everywhere now, even commercials.
See you later.
But…
Wow, just…
Just some rando, huh?
I'm not a rando, man!
[phone buzzing]
Hello, this is rando speaking.
That's me, Hwang Hyun-woo, the rando.
Who?
Gong Ji-tae, the producer?
I know who he is.
I've always been a big fan…
of his variety shows.
A concert
to promote Gangwon as an Expo host?
It's in two weeks
and it's a live broadcast.
I'm reaching out because
we had some cancellations.
[gasps]
Um, Miss Yang,
is there any way I could do it on my own?
I've been doing all my gigs solo lately.
Uh, I was asked
to book all the original members
of Triangle.
To perform the original version
of your first hit song.
[sighs]
You're not on bad terms
with the others, are you?
[scoffs] Oh, yeah.
Huh?
Oh, no, no, no. Uh, that's not it.
I mean, asking them to perform again
out of the blue is, um…
We're planning to have
the concert performers
do a variety show later this year.
How about it?
A variety show?
It's a great opportunity.
Well, then we'll do the show,
you can bet on it.
Ah, geez.
Hyun-woo.
Hwang Hyun-woo.
This is so amazing! [gasps]
-Gosh, how have you been?
-[chuckles]
Hey. [chuckles]
You doing okay?
And who are you?
It's me. Na Tae-poong.
I recognized you right away, you know.
These days,
I'm everywhere you look pretty much.
[chuckles] Jang…
I mean, Tae-poong?
Oh, hey. Yeah, man, it's been so long.
-Yeah. so I guess…
-[chuckles]
…you haven't been doing much…
much TV work lately?
[chuckles]
Well, I'm a singer.
I was just booked for a concert.
You know Gong Ji-tae, right?
It's the one that he's producing. Mmm.
Oh, so you’re doing the show
I turned down?
That's amazing. Cool.
I've got such a hectic schedule
these days,
what with all the gigs and TV work.
It has just been…
So…
What's next on my schedule?
You're going home next.
Oh, I finally get to relax. [chuckles]
Uh, right. Ah…
Okay, well, keep up the good work.
-Okay.
-Okay? Later.
See ya.
[sighs]
Wow.
MEGATON BAR
The guy was practically invisible
back then.
Oh…
I never thought
that the first song I ever wrote
would hit number one like that.
Uh, to our RGB Army,
we love you.
[Sang-gu]
Lung cancer gets you 100 million won.
Liver cancer gets you another 100 million.
Other firms pay out differently
depending on if you have major cancer
or minor cancer.
But things are different at our company.
We don't distinguish between the two.
So whatever type it is,
as long as your cancer
has been diagnosed by a physician…
from that moment on,
you're basically set for life.
Oh, I'm sorry.
We don't actually want you to get sick,
of course. [chuckles]
-[phone ringing]
-Excuse me.
-Oh, sorry about that. So-- Oh, yes?
-Uh, I…
I just need to use the restroom.
Oh, yes, yes. Of course, sir.
Take your time.
[phone ringing]
Ugh, who the hell keeps calling me?
[blows]
Yes, this is Gu Sang-gu.
-[line disconnects]
-Why is that jerk calling?
-How dare he-- Oh…
-[phone ringing]
Quit calling me, you dickhead.
The bastard must think
he's still in charge.
Son of a bitch.
Why's that moron taking so long?
Is he pooping in there?
Some people just love to take a dump
whenever they go out.
Stupid shitheads-- Oh!
[both laughing]
[crying]
[sobbing]
[Hyun-woo] ♪ Say it forward, Gu Sang-gu ♪
♪ Say it backward, Gu Sang-gu ♪
♪ Machine Gun Rapper, Gu Sang-gu ♪
You must be nuts.
You have the balls to show up here?
Well, you said to come over
to your place, didn't you?
Yeah, I told you to come
if you wanted to die.
-[Hyun-woo] See? You invited me over.
-[sighs]
Sang-gu. What do you say?
Gangwon's Expo hosting
promotional concert.
Shut the hell up and get outta here.
Your rapping really was the best,
you know?
Let's get back on that stage again.
What was it you said the last time
we saw each other?
[Hyun-woo]
You ran away without looking back
and let me take the fall
for the plagiarism scandal.
And now you want me
to buy insurance from you?
Hyung, wait. I'm sorry.
Hyung, I'm so hungry.
I hear my stomach talking to me,
it never stops growling. "Growl," it says.
"Growl!" It keeps saying, "Growl."
[sobbing]
Get.
Don't ever show your face to me again.
You said to never show my face
to you again!
I know!
That's why I'm the one
showing my face to you. Yeah?
Sang-gu.
We've had our differences,
but we can just forgive
and move on, hmm?
Let's get the group back together.
-[vehicle approaching]
-Triangle.
Whoa! Okay. Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! [grunting]
Long time no see, Sang-gu.
I almost forgot what you looked like.
I'm so sorry about that, Mr. Ko.
I should've kept in contact with you.
-[chuckles]
-Who's this? A bonus prize?
They were together,
so I brought him as well.
You two close?
Well,
close enough for him to happily
do me a favor and perform together
to promote Gangwon hosting an Expo.
-As close as that.
-[Mr. Ko] So that means…
Oh…
…you two are close enough…
to bear great pain beside each other.
-[gasps]
-No, not really.
Have a nice day.
-Sang-gu.
-Y-Yes?
When are you going to pay me back? The
money from selling insurance is peanuts.
I know, I'm trying,
but I'm only selling insurance
to improve my credit score.
My plan is to get a credit card
so I can max it out
and pay you back as soon
as I possibly can!
You…
have a death wish, don't you?
I really don't, Mr. Ko!
Please don't kill my friend, Mr. Ko.
Tell me how much he owes.
300 million.
Sure thing.
[quivering]
-Hyung, save me. He's gonna kill me.
-300 million's a fortune!
Are you nuts?
What's the deal with this concert
in Gangwon?
I mean, will it make money?
Big industry gig, hot-shot producer…
If we nail the performance,
we could be a regular on his variety show,
start doing gigs. Commercials too.
A big money-maker, for sure.
That Megaton guy,
Na Tae-poong,
he did a variety show, didn't he?
What business is he in?
He was the producer of my solo album.
Not just your album producer.
[Hyun-woo sighs]
-[gags]
-[Mr. Ko] Huh…
You could stage a comeback, right?
[scoffs]
You mean just him, right? [chuckles]
From now on, you two are going to work
hard to pay me back.
-Got it?
-You can't make me.
[grunts]
Pay me!
I will do my best to pay you back.
Hey, man, that hurts.
[breathing heavily]
-Okay, goodbye.
-Yes, thank you.
Who do you think you are
to release a solo album anyway?
Well, I hardly ever got to rap
back when we were in Triangle.
Singing Do-mi, dancing Hyun-woo,
and Sang-gu, the lackey.
My psychiatrist says
it's a number-two complex.
You were number three.
-Oh, yeah…
-You went to an analyst
'cause you couldn't rap
as much as you wanted to?
Don't ever put rap down. Rap is dope, yo!
Okay, we'll add more rapping. Happy now?
Okay, then let me fill the intro,
the outro and the interlude with my rap.
Let's just fill every gap with rap then.
Really?
[gasps] Oh!
-But do you think Do-mi will do it?
-She got married, didn't she?
To a construction company CEO.
It's weird, I never got an invitation.
-I couldn't go to her wedding either.
-You too?
Yeah, I was in jail.
I knew that you'd end up doing drugs.
I'm a gambler, not a druggie! Come on.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
Do-mi! Hey, it's you!
Hey, Byeon Do-mi!
You're Byeon Do-mi, right?
Hey, look! It's me, Hwang Hyun-woo.
Why have you been ignoring my calls?
Hey. No. Hey, let go of me. We're friends.
Hey, Do-mi, Do-mi, Do-mi.
What did I tell you? She knows me.
[sighs] I don't know him.
Get him out of here.
Huh? [grunts] Hey, Byeon Do-mi!
Hey!
[phone buzzes]
HWANG HYUN-WOO
BYEON DO-MI, LET'S GET
THE GROUP BACK TOGETHER!
LET'S DO A CONCERT!
[chuckles]
How cute. Blackmailing me.
Blackmail? Please.
It's just a memento
from the good old days.
How'd you find out where I live,
an investigator?
AI.
Really, AI… told you where I live?
The premium version is awesome.
[sighs] It's true, money is the best, huh?
It's a national live broadcast. Hmm?
You just need to sing
our debut song with us. That's it.
Why would I do that now,
after all these years?
To relive our memories
and reignite our dreams.
Quit the bullshit, will you?
What memories? We don't have any.
You're right.
You always called me out on my bullshit.
Help me out just this once.
I really need this.
This concert's my only hope.
-Please save me.
-[sighs]
Miss Byeon Do-mi.
Do you need money, is that it?
Yeah. Huh? What?
There's no limit on this.
You can use it however you want.
Okay?
Oh.
[sighs]
You know what?
Money's important.
And I need to make money.
But money isn't everything.
This is my dream. The RGB Army needs us.
I'm serious.
Can't you hear it?
The sound of my racing heart?
-I think maybe it will explode.
-[scoffs]
[sighs] Well…
-Whoa, hey.
-Hey! Stop following me.
You want a black eye? Huh?
Thank you.
Hey! [sighs]
Tell the truth. You want to be up
on that stage again. Don't you?
Isn't that why you came to see me?
When people went wild
over our dancing and singing,
that… that feeling! The thrill.
Let's bring back the band
and do it again. Do-mi.
Get lost.
[sighs] Right.
A tycoon's wife can have
whatever she wants.
[mother-in-law] Jun-hoo's new
English kindergarten is unsatisfactory.
Stop sending him there after this week.
And starting next week,
get him ready to start his art prep class.
If you heard me, why don't you answer?
You have absolutely no manners.
I'm sorry, Mother. It's just that…
I have food in my mouth.
I'll be sure to do as you say.
[scoffs]
[sneezes]
Ugh, that's disgusting!
[slurps]
Cover your mouth
when you sneeze from now on.
[sighs] That's so uncivilized. Ugh.
Terribly sorry, Mother.
Ugh, you drive me insane.
Mr. Kang, how's the pruning of the
ornamental trees in the yard progressing?
The new gardener we hired
is quite skilled, ma'am.
That's nice.
Take me outside. Let's take a look.
[scoffs] Ugh, seriously? That's hilarious.
Am I wrong?
[in Korean] ♪ I want to know right now
But the time's not right ♪
♪ You shouldn't do that
You shouldn't do this ♪
♪ Why is it so complicated, baby ♪
♪ Love is, why is it, why is it
So hard? ♪
♪ Even though every day, every day
You still make me laugh and cry ♪
♪ That it will last forever
That it will go on ♪
[in English] I was so awesome back then.
♪ Oh, my love ♪
[in Korean] ♪ Smile at me
With a face full of confidence ♪
HWANG HYUN-WOO
SENT A MESSAGE
♪ Sing to me
With your angelic voice ♪
[sighs]
[message tone chiming repeatedly]
♪ I love you this much
I love you so much it's overflowing ♪
[exhales]
[in English] Do you think it'll be okay
that it's just the two of us?
Hey, if they say no, we'll just have to
get down on our knees and beg.
[exhales]
[Miss Yang] Yes, come in.
[chuckles]
-Uh… Hel--
-Nice to meet you!
-I am-- Huh?
-You're late. Try to be more punctual.
-[Sang-gu] Oh, noona!
-Oh!
-Huh?
-Sorry about that!
[Miss Yang] Have a seat.
This is our producer.
I'm the Dance Machine, DM,
Hwang Hyun-woo.
[shouting] Hello, my name is…
♪ Say it forward, Gu Sang-gu
Say it backward, Gu Sang-gu ♪
A-yo, peace!
[chuckles]
Sing for you…
right now?
Can't you do it?
Well, I mean,
it's not that we can't do it.
-It's just that we probably should--
-No, hey, this is a live broadcast, okay?
So you need to sing for us
before we let you on stage.
-I'm the rapper. Let me rap--
-I get it. You need to hear us sing.
-Oh.
-How about we do it next week?
-I could sing now.
-No.
One moment, please.
[mic voice] Power on.
[upbeat music playing]
[in Korean] ♪ Well hey, should I do this?
Should I do that? ♪
♪ It's clear that's
What is going through your head ♪
♪ Ah, will you just stop and answer me?
I want to know right now ♪
[in English] Oh, she's good.
♪ You shouldn't do that
You shouldn't do this ♪
[Miss Yang] This is fine.
♪ Why is it so complicated, baby ♪
♪ Love is, why is it, why is it
So hard? ♪
-This is my favorite part, right here.
-Oh, yeah, me too.
♪ …every day, every day
You still make me laugh and cry ♪
[Hyun-woo on mic speaker]
♪ That it will last forever ♪
-My part, my part.
-Wow, she's really impressive, huh?
♪ Oh, my love ♪
♪ Smile at me
With a face full of confidence ♪
♪ Call out to me with your… ♪
She sounds exactly the same.
Almost like she has autotune in her voice.
[song continues on speaker]
Is she lip-syncing or something?
Even lip-syncing
would be better than this!
-[Ji-tae] What are you doing?
-[screams]
[grunting]
[Miss Yang] What is he doing?
I'm disappointed.
How can you guys even think about
performing when you're so out of practice?
-Huh?
-[scoffs]
Get your act together.
No, no, it was great.
It was actually better than we expected.
-No.
-Uh…
We have to be at our best for this.
Starting today, we're going into training,
and we vow to make this concert a triumph!
You can depend on… on Triangle…
to get Gangwon its Expo!
Uh, Ms. Yang.
I'm sorry, but could we add
a bit more rap to the song?
-Just a little bit.
-No, we can't.
Just a bit.
No, we need you to do the original song.
[tribal music playing]
SPECIALIZED SERVICE PROVIDER
ANYWHERE IN THE COUNTRY
SPECIALIZED HUNTER
OF NUISANCE WILDLIFE
Ah…
Which floor is the variety show on?
Sorry?
Take good care of her while I'm gone.
[Miss Yang gasps]
Is this it?
Uh…
Are you the ones who called me?
[Ji-tae] Wh-Who is he?
-Uh…
-Who are you?
[Miss Yang] Uh…
Are you by any chance Choi Seong-gon?
Do you get a lot of dangerous wildlife
at TV stations these days?
Like wild boar, water deer.
He doesn't know?
I don't… I just set up the meeting.
I couldn't reach him directly
-to explain what it was about.
-[Ji-tae sighs]
Uh…
So, uh, Gangwon is hoping
to host the Expo,
and, uh, we'd like you to perform at the
promotional concert, Mr. Choi Seong-gon.
Concert?
Uh…
[Seong-gon] Say that again.
What did you just say to me?
Uh, s-so, we're, uh…
We're organizing a promotional concert
to support Gangwon's bid to host the Expo
and we would like you to perform.
So you're saying…
[breathes shakily]
…I can perform in front of my fans again?
Well, see, it's a live broadcast.
We're planning it.
So there's a lot of details
we haven't worked out yet.
Sir, I've been longing to sing again.
R-Right,
but we need to ensure that
your performance will meet our standards
before we put you on sta--
[in Korean] ♪ I like you ♪
♪ I like you ♪
♪ I like you because you're pretty ♪
[backup] ♪ Because you're pretty ♪
♪ I like you ♪
♪ I like you because you're kind ♪
[backup] ♪ Because you're kind ♪
♪ I like you ♪
♪ I like you because you're funny ♪
[backup] ♪ Because you're funny ♪
♪ I like you ♪
♪ I like you so much I could die ♪
♪ You like me too ♪
♪ We like each other ♪
♪ Ooh, ah, ooh-ah ♪
[song fades]
[humming]
[shudders]
[in English] No.
This isn't Choi Seong-gon.
This man is no knight in shining armor.
But…
I prefer my current style.
[horns honking]
Ballads are all about skill.
[in Korean] ♪ I like you ♪
[in English] I rent a rehearsal room
even though I'm almost broke,
and these guys just… [clicks tongue]
[line ringing]
Hey, where are you, bro?
[horn honks]
[Sang-gu] Yeah, I'll call you later.
[sighs]
Hey.
What's all this?
Mr. Hong is clearing out his storage room,
so he told me
I should take my albums and go to hell.
But I thought his name was Mr. Ko.
Mr. Ko did the first album.
This one's the second.
I just… wanted to prove myself.
What are you trying to prove exactly?
Where was this?
-LA.
-Why?
Hip-hop's hometown.
The truth is, when I was in Triangle,
my mom always wondered
why I was in the background.
[crying] In a corner, like some lackey.
She said it was upsetting.
-Hey, let's just go in and practice.
-[crying]
Oh, Mom…
He's right though. Hyung is right.
Suck it up now, Gu Sang-gu!
Yo, baby!
[upbeat music playing]
One, two, three, four.
Gu Sang-gu, baby, gotta give it up.
[vocalizing]
GU SANG-GU DRIVE IT IN
[mother-in-law]
What the hell have you been doing lately?
For heaven's sake, answer me! You little…
[sighs] Are you even
listening to me right now, huh?
[grunts]
[groaning]
♪ Yo, if you get diagnosed with cancer
You'll be livin' like a gangster ♪
♪ You bank a hundred million won
If you get cancer of the lung ♪
♪ Just sign the line ♪
[shouts]
SANG-GU
-Noona!
-Hey! What took you so long?
Hey. Did I or did I not tell you guys
to email me your practice videos, huh?
Why haven't you done that?
-Hey, Gu Sa--
-[hip-hop playing through earphones]
[sighs]
Do-mi, did you memorize your choreo?
Sort of.
S-Sort of?
Damn, I'm hungry.
Let's stop somewhere
and get something to eat.
You did it, didn't you?
You must've done it.
Hot dog.
Your leader asked you to.
-Hot bar.
-So I'm sure you did it.
And tteokbokki.
Sure.
-[server] Enjoy.
-Ah, thank you.
Here you go, milady.
I'm sure you're used to much better food
than this, but that's all they've got.
-Hmm?
-It's okay.
I'm not an actual rich person quite yet.
It's more like
I'm a rich-person groupie right now.
A rich-person groupie, huh?
That makes me feel jealous,
but at the same time…
a little sad. Hmm?
Hey, who are you to feel sad for me?
You threw your pride and dignity
out the window
so you could be in the spotlight
one more time.
Hey. Pride doesn't pay the bills, okay?
Besides, if you two hadn't ditched me
and took off back then,
I could've kept my pride intact.
Hang on… We ditched you?
You think we ditched you?
You guys signed up with that other agency
and I had to fend for myself.
That is exactly…
exactly what happened, huh?
I can't believe you remember all that.
It was so long ago.
How do you do it? Mmm.
[toilet flushes]
[sighs]
So do you think
Do-mi will want to keep performing?
Why would she?
But who knows?
Once the adrenaline hits her,
-she might get hooked, you know?
-Oh, noona…
Hyung, wait a minute.
That guy looks really familiar,
but I can't figure out
where I know him from.
Hey, he looks familiar to me too.
[Sang-gu] Where was it? He could be
from one of the networks I guess.
-[Hyun-woo] Maybe.
-[grunts]
[sighs]
Hey. That's Park Yong-gu.
-Hey, hold on.
-Hey!
-Oh!
-Hyah!
[grunts]
Park Yong-gu!
[police siren blares]
Okay, listen carefully
to what I'm about to say.
This man is not Mr. Park Yong-gu.
He is Mr. Emiliano Scaloni.
And he's not Korean either.
He's Argentinian.
Look at this passport. See?
This makes no sense.
Hey, you're Park Yong-gu.
Tell them who you are!
No soy coreano. Soy argentino!
No! You're Park Yong-gu
from Yong-gu Records,
who pocketed all our profits
and skipped the country!
[speaking Spanish]
You think I wouldn't recognize you
just because you have a fake mustache…
-and speak a foreign language?
-[screams]
-That's gotta sting.
-What do you think you're doing?
You can't treat foreigners that way!
[whimpering, speaking Spanish]
Hey, the mustache looks real.
Listen to me!
Do you want to go to police? To sue?
No police!
I'm busy man, I have
a business very important.
[speaking Spanish]
Okay, okay.
Welcome to Korea, Mr. Scaloni. Bye-bye!
-Gracias.
-Okay!
-You screwed up my--
-Hyung!
-Sir! Leave the man alone!
-I got him!
BMW 9841
NAVY BLUE MERCEDES-BENZ 8340
[Hyun-woo] It was him.
That was Mr. Park, for sure.
All right, so suppose it was
Mr. Park, what do we do now?
We get our revenge. What else?
He's the reason I ended up like this.
Oh! Hey.
Isn't that Mr. Park's car just up ahead?
-Yes! Come on!
-[gasps]
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
-[Hyun-woo] We need to catch him!
-[Sang-gu] Geez, seriously? No, don't!
-Don't!
-[Do-mi] Step on it. We're gonna lose him.
-I'm getting my money back no matter what.
-[Sang-gu] Step on it? Step on what?
-[Do-mi] Faster!
-Are you crazy?
-What do you mean, step on it, noona?
-Speed up! Come on!
-[Sang-gu] No, you can't. Hey, stop.
-[Do-mi] Closer, closer, closer. Come on!
I'm gonna catch up with you.
-We got him, we got him.
-[Do-mi] Yeah. Faster!
-[Sang-gu] Oh, God, don't. Slow down.
-[Do-mi] Let's go!
-[Sang-gu] Slow down. Don't.
-[scream]
Just stop, please!
You're mine!
-Almost there, almost there, almost…
-Jesus, slow down.
We're too close. We're gonna crash.
-[Do-mi] Hey you!
-We're gonna get in an accident.
-We have a concert! Snap out of it!
-You think I wouldn't recognize you?
[Do-mi] Hey, Park Yong-gu!
Give me my money! Pay me what you owe me!
-Ram him! Now!
-[Sang-gu] Oh, no. Whoa.
-What the hell are you talking about?
-[Do-mi] Do it!
-Are you nuts?
-[Do-mi] Almost got him!
Y-Y-You want me to? You sure?
-Seriously! Don't do it!
-Come on!
-Stop the car now.
-[Do-mi] No, it's fine.
-I'm gonna ram him now!
-Hyung, are you outta your mind?
-This is crazy!
-Hurry up, come on. Ram him now!
[Sang-gu] No!
[all shouting]
-[gasps]
-[gasps] Oh, God…
[gasps]
I warned you, hyung.
[gasps] Hyun-woo,
I think you're totally screwed.
-What do we do?
-[all gasp]
[Sang-gu] What do we do?
-Oh, no. Oh, no!
-[Sang-gu] What do we do?
-[shouts]
-Hey, hey! [yelps]
-Oh, shit, oh, shit.
-[Do-mi] Hold on!
-Whoa, Hey, Hey! Wait for us!
-[Sang-gu] It's steep!
[grunts]
[grunting]
Come on!
I got you!
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
-[yelps] Oh!
-Hey, Mr. Park, are you okay?
[gasps]
-He's alive. He's alive, he's alive.
-He's alive?
-He's alive.
-Should we call an ambulance?
Well, of course we should.
Why are you asking me?
You were driving
the car that almost killed him.
You're gonna be the one they arrest.
So it's not my decision,
it's up to you if we call or not.
-They'll arrest me?
-Of course.
But you were the one who egged me on.
-Right-- Huh?
-[scream] Oh, my God!
I think we made eye contact.
-Oh!
-Huh?
[Sang-gu] Hmm?
What the…
You sure you weren't seeing things?
I'll try slapping him.
Stop, don't!
What if he's actually injured?
You could hurt him even more.
Let's get him in the car for now.
Either we take him to the hospital…
-Or we bury him in the hills.
-Yeah, good idea, the hills.
Wait. No, no, no, no. I didn't say that.
[all grunting]
-Oh, my gosh.
-Oh, man, he's heavy.
[Do-mi] Oh!
-[Hyun-woo] Look out!
-[Do-mi] No, no, no, no, no, no.
-I lost my grip.
-[Hyun-woo] You have to hold him tightly!
-[Sang-gu] I was holding on tightly.
-[Hyun-woo] Come on! Run! Let's get him!
[all grunting, panting]
-[Do-mi] What do we do? Oh!
-[Hyun-woo] Oh, shit.
-What do we do?
-Grab him, noona!
[band members grunting]
geez!
-[Do-mi screams] He's rolling away again.
-[Hyun-woo] No!
-Ah! Why do you keep losing your grip?
-[Do-mi] Over there!
[band members grunting, panting]
[Do-mi] I'm not doing this.
[grunting continues]
-Ugh.
-Oh, set him down.
[Sang-gu] Damn! [breathing heavily]
Was I wrong?
-[Hyun-woo panting]
-He hasn't opened his eyes once.
Hyung, what if you dropped him
so many times, he actually died?
-I was holding on tight.
-[horn honks]
[yelps]
-Look out!
-[Do-mi screams]
[all groaning]
I'm sorry! I'm still a rookie driver!
A rookie?
And you…
you drive that, and you're a rookie?
Hey! You need to watch where you're going!
Are you okay? Is anybody hurt?
I didn't kill anybody, did I?
-Oh, please say no one died. [wailing]
-Whoa, yeah, no one died, okay?
-No one's hurt either.
-[Do-mi] Okay okay!
-Right.
-[whimpering, crying]
[Do-mi sighs]
It's okay.
I'll call the police.
I'll turn myself in.
Nonsense! No need. Put your phone down.
Uh-huh.
Put that phone away right now!
You're bleeding, though.
Please, at least let me call
my insurance company, sir.
[grunts]
It's okay,
driving is risky. People get hurt.
And sometimes they bleed, you know?
Well… what about what I did to your car?
You don't need
to concern yourself with that.
Please, go now.
Wait a minute.
You guys…
look familiar.
I know you.
He sings.
You rap…
Right?
I can rap, but he can't sing.
Byeon Do-mi, in the early 2000s
you were in…Tambourine.
Right?
Xylophone.
-Triangle, dude.
-Triangle!
Oh! Oh! Oh! [gasping]
I see what's happening. I'll post about it
all over social media.
What, what, what? Post what?
This wholesome celebrity story.
Best idea ever!
You should go right now
and post that wholesome story.
-[driver] Of course.
-[Hyun-woo] Okay, up you go.
That's all right.
Just go.
Counting on you.
Post that wholesome story!
Hey, this whole thing can be fixed.
Don't give up now.
We've got a wholesome story,
now we just need to nail the performance.
Where the hell did he go?
[Sang-gu] Huh?
-[Do-mi] Huh?
-[Hyun-woo] Huh?
-Oh, sh-- [gasp]
-[Do-mi] Shit.
-[Sang-gu] Wait. What?
-[Do-mi] What happened?
-Guess he wasn't dead.
-[grunts]
-Huh?
There he is.
Where?
-Park Yong-gu!
-[Mr. Park yelps]
[Hyun-woo] Stop right there!
[speaking Spanish]
[screaming]
[Seong-gon humming]
[vocalizing]
[grunts, exclaims]
[in English] Big ones like that are rare.
NUISANCE WILDLIFE WANTED FOR
CAUSING CROP DAMAGE, HUMAN INJURIES
Holy shit.
No way.
I'm not a hunter any more, I'm a singer.
Settle down.
[in Korean] ♪ I like you ♪
♪ I like you ♪
[grunt]
[boar grunting]
♪ I like you ♪
[shouting in Spanish]
[whimpering]
[in English] I just want to talk to you!
Hey!
Today's a big day for me.
Let's just talk, okay?
[breathing heavily]
[boar grunting]
[shouting in Spanish]
[grunting]
[panting]
Come on! [pants]
Hey.
Where'd he go?
[panting]
-[gasps]
-[boar squeals]
He just disappeared.
[sighs] Damn it.
[breathing heavily]
[gasping]
What did I do?
Excuse me.
You're not dead, are you?
You can't die. You can't die.
Hang in there.
Wait…
Another arrest…
Was this your first time?
If not, when did you start using?
Have you been diagnosed
with exhibitionism?
-Never.
-[footsteps approaching]
[grunts]
Who is that bastard?
[Hyun-woo] Who is this bastard?
[chuckles] Hi there.
[Seong-gon] He's suspicious.
Hi, how ya doin'?
-[chuckles]
-[Hyun-woo] He's sketchy.
[inhales deeply] I'm good.
Just out for a walk. [chuckles]
Same.
A walk, here?
Just walking.
[both chuckle]
[Hyun-woo] Is he some kind of psycho?
Have we met…
before…
Now that you mention it,
I think we might've run into each other…
before…
[boar shrieks in distance]
-Did you do that?
-[exclaims] No! It wasn't me!
[grunting]
[Do-mi] Hey, what are you doing?
Put your back into it.
[engine sputters, stops]
-[Do-mi sighs]
-[engine sputtering]
[grunting]
Noona, I can't!
Ugh! This car's dead.
[Sang-gu grunts] Noona.
-Noona, I feel dizzy.
-Oh, geez.
-Enough already.
-[sighs]
-[both sigh]
-[vehicle approaching]
Noona, my head feels funny.
[Do-mi] Who's in that piece of shit?
[Sang-gu] Wait…
[Miss Yang] Hello, Mr. Hyun-woo.
When can we expect you?
The rehearsal is starting soon
and Mr. Oh is looking for you.
[Hyun-woo] Oh, really, he is?
Oh, that's okay, we are totally prepared,
and so no rehearsal will be needed.
[chuckles]
You're not running late, are you?
Oh, gosh,
no, we're definitely not running late.
Hello, Choi Seong-gon speaking.
I will also be late.
Oh, uh,
Mr. Seong-gon is with you, too, is he?
Yeah, uh-huh.
We're coming together.
[Miss Yang] Did he just say
that you're going to be late?
Mr. Hyun-woo,
you cannot be late. You can't.
Sorry about that, see ya.
What about Mr. Park?
What's the plan?
Did you see any bullet holes in him?
Go check him out. I bet he was shot.
I told you that I didn't shoot the guy.
Don't try to pin this on me.
Well, the police will be able
to figure out if you're guilty or not.
Yeah, let's go to the police station.
The police?
Why the police? [breathes shakily]
Are you threatening me,
after all the good times we had together?
You're crazy,
we never had any good times together.
Yeah, we had to disband
-because of what you did!
-Yeah!
No, that was
because you plagiarized a song.
Plagiarized? Wait, it was drugs and pla…
I think he might be right, hyung.
-It was because of the plagiarism.
-Oh, shit.
-What? What? Did he get shot?
-What?
[Do-mi] I just made eye contact with him.
Oh, he's awake?
No, he's… [gasps]
…uh, I think he's trying
to trick us again.
I'm pretty sure he's
just pretending to be unconscious.
[officer] West Interchange Control Center,
emergency dispatch.
Traffic accident reported.
A vehicle-to-vehicle collision resulting
in a fall has been reported.
At San 58, Jucheon-ro, Seobu-gu, Gangwon.
Assess the scene,
take necessary actions, and report back.
[officer] Unit four has arrived at
the scene. We have identified the vehicle.
Plate number 8340… 834…
It's that damn Benz from earlier!
-[siren wailing]
-[gasps]
The police are on our tail.
[all gasp]
Everybody get down now!
-[gasps]
-Oh!
[siren continues]
Wait, what the hell?
This guy is nuts.
[breathing shakily]
Hey, what are you doing?
You need to drive!
[Sang-gu] Is this a Tesla?
Hey, you need to pull over. You hear?
Hm.
I said, pull over.
[grunts]
Ah…
Are you out of your mind?
Who are you people, huh?
[Hyun-woo inhales deeply]
[Sang-gu] Uh…
[sighs, chuckles]
[Sang-gu] Did you find it?
[chuckles]
You're the ones from earlier.
Oh, hi, how are you?
-Hello.
-[Do-mi chuckles]
Oh, we're late for a gig,
so we really need to get going.
-[chuckles]
-We're singers, actually.
[chuckles]
Don't you recognize me?
Endless Charm Byeon Do-mi.
-Sound familiar? [chuckles]
-Peace.
Uh-huh….
Uh-huh.
Are you a singer too?
You caught me.
Love you. [chuckles]
[gulps]
[Seong-gon] Hm?
[breathing shakily]
[officer] What is that?
What?
[both chuckle]
And what is that thing?
[stammers] This is just a gun
that was here.
-[officer] Freeze!
-[yelps]
-[stammering] What's wrong?
-[Do-mi screams]
Put down the gun and show your hands!
-[screaming]
-Put the gun down, and… hands, hands!
-I'm sorry.
-The gun, the gun.
-This man's the owner. It's his, it's his.
-Yeah, it's my gun, sir.
Yeah, yeah, I'm a hunter.
-You said "singer."
-Currently, I'm a hunter.
-Get those clothes out of the way.
-Okay. Okay, I'll move them. Okay.
-[gasps] No, no, no, no.
-But-- But--
What the hell?
-You people murdered that guy?
-[Do-mi] No!
No, no, he's not dead,
he's just pretending.
He's actually okay.
[all screaming, gasping]
[officer]
Take your hands off the wheel and get out.
-The next shot is a live round!
-Okay, we'll get out.
We'll get out, we'll get out.
-We just need to get to our gig.
-[officer] You're not going to any gig.
-We're bringing you in.
-Bringing us in?
I'm not going through that again!
-[Do-mi screams]
-[officer] Whoa! Whoa! Hey, you!
[grunting]
Get 'em! Get 'em!
What do you think you're doing, man?
The last time they took me in,
I lost 20 years of my life. [sighs]
I'm not letting it happen again.
Think about what you're doing.
We won't be able to do the show now.
Hey, forget about the show.
-We're in trouble here.
-[phone buzzes]
Shut up!
-Hello, we're almost there. We're in… um…
-[sighs]
…downtown Gangwon.
[Do-mi] Hey, are you okay?
[sighs] That's not the point.
Hurry up,
Mr. Gong is really mad right now.
-Uh-huh. Oh, is that right?
-[Do-mi] Wake up! Damn it.
Hey, Gu Sang-gu! Snap out of it!
[Miss Yang] Come on,
this is being aired live.
-You can't be late like this.
-[sighs]
[groans] He'll replace you with the backup
group if you're late to rehearsal.
I see. Is that so?
Tell them not to bother showing up here.
Hey, hey. Hey, don't even think
about showing up here, damn it!
[Miss Yang] Just get here! Hurry, hurry!
We're gonna get there on time.
-Consider that a promise.
-[Ji-tae] Don't come!
-Don't come!
-[Miss Yang] Just hurry up!
-Step on it.
-[growls]
Hey, can we just give up
and go home already?
I said step on it, now!
Let's go!
[siren wailing]
Oh! Shit, there they are.
Are you using live rounds?
I told you, I saw a dead body.
Those guys are real murderers.
Wee-oo, wee-oo. Look, the police
are coming, stop! Better pull over.
No way, we don't have time.
We're supposed to be there already.
Come on, we have
to catch these guys. Move closer!
[screams]
That son of bitch is shooting at us!
[Do-mi screaming]
Oh, shit.
[Do-mi crying]
-[yelping]
-[officer] Stop the car!
Stop the car!
[horn blaring]
-Whoa! Watch out!
-[officers exclaim]
[screaming]
They could've killed us.
What's their problem, anyway?
You're their problem, you idiot!
Yeah, but we didn't do anything wrong.
It's their fault
for shooting at us willy nilly.
They're gonna let us perform, aren't they?
There's this new rap I wrote, and I told
my mother I'd be doing it at the concert.
[Do-mi] Why would you write a new rap?
'Cause I'll be rapping during the intro,
the outro
and the interlude, didn't you know?
Shut up! No, you're not!
Okay, look, we're doing the original song.
-Yeah.
-Hey, wait a minute.
Does that mean you lied to me?
Let's just get there,
so we can do this concert, okay?
And next time you can rap
as much as you want.
Next time?
So then, you did lie to me, didn't you?
Let's focus on doing
the best show that we can today, okay?
So you lied, you bastard!
You son of a bitch,
-you always do this to me!
-Hey. [growls]
Right now,
it just really isn't that important!
Let's just get
to the venue and deal with it later!
-No, you son of a bitch.
-[screaming]
-[growls]
-Ah, stop it!
-Hey, Hwang Hyun-woo!
-Please don't.
You're the one
who's supposed to be our leader,
but you act like a little boy.
-[breathing heavily]
-And, Gu Sang-gu,
your rapping wouldn't be an issue,
if you weren't so damn bad at it!
[screams] This is what I get
for working with losers!
-Ugh, I need a smoke right now.
-I'm screwed.
-geez.
-I think my third album's gonna tank.
Damn it.
[breathing heavily]
Don't tell me you signed another contract.
I've got to prove I can do it.
What do you need to prove?
Why do you keep saying that?
What son of a bitch put
that idea in your head?
Which one
of those rotten stinking producers was it?
-It was my dad.
-What?
He tried to help me and he ended up…
mortgaging the house.
He couldn't make the payments…
Fuck my life. [crying]
He lost the house trying
to save his talentless son.
-[sighs]
-[Sang-gu] Oh, it's all my fault. [crying]
What's going on?
What's wrong with my car?
-[exclaiming]
-[Hyun-woo] Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Hey, hey, stop, stop, stop, stop! No!
[all screaming]
What the hell?
[all grunt]
DANGER
[all groaning]
[phone buzzing]
Oh.
Uh, hello there,
Miss Yang, we'll be there soon.
How dare you be late for my show?
You must be completely insane!
And there's absolutely no way
that you'll work with me again!
Please don't do this, Mr. Gong, please.
-Please…
-I'm hanging up, damn it!
[line disconnects]
Okay, uh,
get the backup group ready.
They're already on their way.
Who? Are they famous?
Th-They're coming right now.
You know them, right, Mr. Gong?
Kong Kong Girls.
Would you make them
go away now, please?
-That's right, turn around, go back.
-Please go now. Yes, I'm sorry. Please go.
Could you just quit jumping and walk out?
-Mr. Gong. Um…
-Too much thumping.
Mr. Na Tae-poong is doing
a gig nearby, and he just told me
-he could make it here for the finale.
-N-Na Tae-poong?
Tell him we want him.
Tell him to get over here right now.
-Yes, sir. Got it.
-Be quick about it!
[Seong-gon] It's over.
I can kiss my comeback goodbye.
It's over.
What is it they say?
We all get three big chances in life?
No, you're wrong.
Why would life give anybody
three whole chances?
Should've grabbed the first one
when it came to you. [scoffs]
[Sang-gu] ♪ Life keeps makin'
A fool outta me ♪
♪ As I try to make it big in the scene ♪
♪ I lit my rocket
And it crashed to earth again ♪
♪ Shattered beats surround me
As I lay on the land ♪
♪ But still, I'll rise from the ashes
Spittin' rhymes until the end ♪
-Are you okay?
-[sighs]
Take it easy, man.
Take it easy?
♪ You guys need to get a mirror
So y'all can take a look ♪
♪ Your singing is so bad
It makes my rap sound good ♪
No, you still suck at rapping.
Do you even know
what a rhyme is, or what? Huh?
♪ Freestyle’s how I kick it
Ya dig it? ♪
♪ If that's freestyle rap
Then even I could be a star ♪
♪ Just make the last word rhyme
It'll really take you far ♪
♪ Maybe I should give it a try ♪
♪ Instead of being the ballad guy ♪
♪ I think I'm through
Love you ♪
Get outta here, you're annoying.
♪ Oh, I can freestyle here ♪
♪ And I can freestyle there ♪
♪ I can freestyle high
And I can freestyle low ♪
♪ I could do fast rap, rap, rap ♪
♪ Or do it real slow ♪
-Don't try to imitate me like that.
-Ooh.
[Sang-gu]
It's offensive, you jerk. Stop it.
♪ Yo! ♪
♪ Whose fault is it
This is how we ended up? ♪
♪ Yo! ♪
♪ And why's the leader
By himself just sitting in the truck? ♪
♪ Pass! ♪
Hey, leader.
Won't you say something? Come on!
[grunts]
[sighing]
[Do-mi] Hey, what's wrong with you?
I think the accident scrambled
their brains.
I think they've gone crazy.
-[phone buzzing]
-[Hyun-woo grunts]
Hello, Miss Yang.
We're almost there,
it'll just be a minute.
-[Miss Yang] Really?
-We're right in front of the venue.
[Miss Yang] If you aren't,
we'll have a backup singer perform.
Okay.
See you in a minute.
You only get
three big opportunities in life.
That's way too few.
It's not fair!
It's easy to screw up
three opportunities in your life.
Shouldn't we get at least
a few dozen chances?
Shouldn't that be how it is?
It doesn't matter if there's a war,
or an alien invasion,
we're getting on that stage today!
You hear that, Byeon Do-mi?
-Huh?
-You need to perform
on that stage
at least once while were all together.
-Uh-huh.
-Hey, Gu Sang-gu!
Do you want to do your rap, or not?
I want to do all of it, hyung! Let's go!
Why don't you answer me,
Choi Seong-gon, you bastard?
-You wanna go on stage?
-Of course I do, you bastard.
The car's busted.
Look familiar? It's a car.
They pass by here all the time.
It's now or never.
We have to hurry, team. Go now!
Now or never?
Okay. Oh, this…
Hey, this is yours.
Oh! Hey,
hey, hey, hey, look, this isn't right.
Hwang Hyun-woo,
no matter how much you want
to perform, you can't resort to crime!
Ooh!
Haven't you heard of hitchhiking?
[growl] Damn it.
-Here. Whoa, whoa.
-geez!
[sighs] What are we going to do about him?
Hey. I know we made eye contact.
He's just pretending to be unconscious!
[sighs] But I don't get
why he's keeping this up.
Mr. Park.
If you've been pretending
to be unconscious this whole time
because of the money you owe us,
let's just call it even
so we can all move on.
It's water under the bridge.
We absolve you of your past actions
forever, okay?
-Okay, that'll do!
-[all gasp]
-What the-- Holy shit.
-Oh, my God!
All right, all right, all right.
What's wrong with my neck?
[laughs] Hey, guys,
in South America,
old school K-pop is trending again.
I'm gonna pick a few groups
at the concert to take back with me.
I didn't realize you guys were performing.
He's still the same greedy asshole.
Let's go. We've got a show to do.
-[chuckles]
-[Hyun-woo] Let's go.
Over here.
-Over here.
Ta-da, yoo-hoo!
-[sighs]
-[Sang-gu] Huh?
-[officer] Hands up!
-[gasps]
-You're under arrest for murder!
-Freeze!
Who did they kill?
Officer, am I not being clear?
I wasn't looking where I was going
and I smashed into their car.
And they wanted to make sure I was okay.
I thought you only spoke Spanish.
I'd just gotten so dang used to it.
But ever since my return,
I've been using it less and less.
It's sort of like riding a bike again.
You get rusty, but after a while,
it all just starts to come back.
[in Korean] ♪ I like you ♪
♪ I like you ♪
♪ Because you're pretty ♪
-Yo!
-♪ I like you ♪
[vocalizes]
♪ Read it forward, Gu Sang-gu
Backward, still Gu Sang-gu ♪
♪ Love is, why is it, why is it
So hard? ♪
-♪ That it will go on, promise me ♪
-♪ Gu Sang-gu, the unstoppable rapper ♪
[all singing, vocalizing]
♪ Look at me, I'm cool ♪
GANGWON CIVIC GYMNASIUM
Shit, we can't stop now. We have to run.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry!
-[Sang-gu] Go, go!
-Come on!
Seriously, what are we even doing?
-Let's go.
-Yeah.
-I'll never get another chance like this!
-What? Hold on!
-[Seong-gon yells]
-Let's go.
Hurry up! Catch him!
Hey, don't you want to do the show?
Run like your life depends on it!
Faster, let's go! Come on! come on!
[growling]
Okay, this way, come on.
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la
Wonderful liar, you are… ♪
Goddamn it, where are they?
What the hell's going on?
-[all panting]
-I'm sorry.
Were you guys fighting each other in here?
Let's go, come on!
We need you on stage right now!
-Come on, hurry up! Let's go!
-Hang on. Let us catch our breath first.
-No, we do not have…
-[grunts]
I got lost and had to come around
the back way…
-Hey, let him go first.
-Ah! Yeah, okay.
Let's get him on stage right now,
hurry up!
-Me first?
-It's okay,
all you have to do is stand there
and sing.
-I just need to sing.
-You got this. You're a professional.
-[Seong-gon] I'm a professional.
-Yes, a professional.
All right, so, pay attention.
After you’re done singing,
do you all remember
what you're supposed to say?
[all] "We sincerely support
Gangwon's bid to host the Expo."
Yes, that line is the most important.
It's more important than your song.
Got it? Got it?
-Don't forget to say it, okay?
-[panting]
-Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
-Okay.
Hey, listen,
did they get into some kinda trouble
on the way here? Huh?
-What?
-Didn't you notice? I mean,
they're obviously exhausted,
they've got wild eyes.
Maybe a car accident or something?
What if they caused it?
Then what do we do?
Huh?
Oh, geez, I mean, what if
they killed someone in a hit and run?
It could be the end
of my entire career, okay?
Well, what can we do?
Choi Seong-gon will be going on
any second now.
-[slow pop music playing]
-The song's starting. You need to go now.
-Oh, uh, that's my song. That's my song.
-Yeah.
[in Korean] ♪ I like you ♪
[backup singer] ♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ I like you ♪
[Ji-tae] How are things going?
Oh, no… Is he on drugs again?
What's wrong with this guy?
-[backup singer] ♪ Because you're pretty ♪
-♪ I like you ♪
♪ I like you because you're kind-- ♪
[retching]
[backup singer] ♪ Because you're kind ♪
-So now we're implicated in drug use, too.
-[crowd murmuring]
♪ I like you because you're funny ♪
[assistant]
Mr. Gong, Mr. Na Tae-poong is here.
-♪ I like you ♪
-Triangle is out.
Get Na Tae-poong ready to go on.
♪ I like you so much I could die-- ♪
[retching]
Ugh, geez!
Oh, that's so gross.
HUMAN SUGAR, CHOI SEONG-GON,
WE LOVE YOU
[Ji-tae] He's turning around. He's puking!
He's turning and puking!
That son of a bitch is turning around
while he pukes!
[breathing heavily] Whoo!
♪ When we met for the third time, I knew ♪
[crowd murmuring]
♪ That you and I felt the same way ♪
[grunting]
-A little faster, please.
-Oh, yeah, yeah.
[Tae-poong vocalizes]
[Seong-gon]
♪ …even though you weren't sure… ♪
-Be right back.
-Yes, he'll be going on shortly. Okay.
Tae-poong.
Hey, wh-what are you doing here?
[Seong-gon] ♪ I like you ♪
Uh…
I-I'm a singer, so I came here to sing.
Did you think I was here
to clean up poop? [chuckles]
B-Because I'm not a janitor.
Yeah, well,
they probably have a lot of janitors.
♪ I like you, I like you so much
I could die ♪
♪ I like you ♪
Hyun-woo.
Triangle…
won't be going on today.
No way.
Hey, tell him my group's going up next.
Um, well,
Mr. Gong says he's going on next.
You go ahead, I'll be right there.
-I'll be right behind.
-Okay, please hurry.
-Give me a minute.
-Hey, uh…
[Seong-gon continues on stage]
What was that thing again?
You were always
doing this hand gesture.
Oh, a triangle.
Did you think Triangle
would get to perform the finale,
when no one knows who you are?
Tae-poong.
This concert will be our last hurrah.
We need to get up on that stage.
-So come on…
-[Seong-gon retching]
What do you say? I'm begging you.
Please let us do it, Tae-poong.
Wow. You finally got my name right.
Well, your name is cool.
Oh, no, no. You…
You guys always treated me
like I was nothing back in the day.
And when you saw me recently,
you didn't recognize me, right?
I recognized you immediately, you know?
I'm quite a bit more famous
than you now, aren't I?
So how is it
that you didn't recognize me that day?
It was a misunderstanding.
The truth is, we…
We were jealous of your talent
and good looks,
-so we made fun of you all the time.
-Bullshit!
The truth is,
you're so desperate to perform,
you'll say anything to get back
on that stage.
We were all huge Megaton fans
and that's the truth.
-Stop bullshitting me.
-I'm serious.
[Seong-gon] ♪ When we met for the 4th time
I shyly told you how I felt ♪
♪ And held your hand ♪
♪ I like you ♪
♪ I like you because you're pretty ♪
♪ I like you because you're kind ♪
[footsteps running]
Hey!
Who's the bastard they're putting on
instead of us? Huh?
Is it this guy?
A lounge singer?
Hyung, hyung,
the Megaton guy is gonna replace us!
He's on his way now.
We have to stop him before
he gets here. Come on!
Quiet, damn it!
It's not like that, Jang-poong.
The truth is I can't believe you guys
haven't changed.
You're still assholes, huh?
Hate to break it to you,
but your performance is canceled.
All right? So, go away. Beat it.
-Go home.
-Ja-Jang-poong… Ah…
Tae-poong.
I had one chance to succeed,
and I totally screwed it up.
[groaning]
What do I do now? I'm a ballad singer.
Tae-poong. Hey, Tae-poong, please…
ARTIST ROUTE
-Tae-poong, just this once.
-Wait, Tae-poong's the Megaton guy?
For just a single performance
we went through…
such a terribly horrendous ordeal.
Let's just do it.
What?
I just wanted one more performance.
Was that too much to ask for?
-No. Get back.
-You're not allowed.
[screams]
[Hyun-woo] Hurry, move!
Please enjoy the rest of the concert.
Our next act is standing by
to entertain you.
[MC] So let me give him
a proper introduction.
The last performer of the evening
is too popular a celebrity
to be referred to simply as
a retro singer.
[Do-mi] Hurry, hurry.
From Megaton…
Uh-- Oh, ah, okay…
-Th-There seems to be--
-Hello, to all of you!
That's right, it's Byeon Do-mi, and I…
have returned!
♪ Say it forward, Gu Sang-gu
Say it backward, Gu Sang-gu ♪
Hello there, I'm the leader of Triangle,
the Dance Machine, DM, Hwang Hyun-woo.
And are you all ready for a crazy show?
They're outta their minds.
I should have known. Shit.
What was that? I can't hear you.
-Whoo!
-Yeah, come on everybody, let's go!
-Everyone, put your hands up!
-[Do-mi] Yeah! Put your hands up!
Sir, sir! Oh!
-[Do-mi] Make some noise!
-Woo-hoo!
[crowd murmuring]
[Miss Yang]
Mr. Gong, this is a huge mistake.
But we've got no choice,
so, let's just play the backing track.
[Ji-tae] Those idiots definitely
got into some trouble.
[laughs] My career is about
to end here and now.
[murmuring continues]
[in Korean] ♪ Love is, why is it
Why is it so hard? ♪
♪ Triangle ♪
♪ Even though every day, every day
You still make me laugh and cry ♪
-♪ That it will last forever ♪
-♪ Forever ♪
♪ That it will go on ♪
-♪ Promise me, my love ♪
-♪ My love ♪
-♪ Oh, my love ♪
♪ Smile at me
With a face full of confidence ♪
♪ Hey, hey! ♪
♪ Call out to me with your angelic voice ♪
♪ Angel
I love you I love you this much ♪
[Sang-gu] ♪ Sing it, sing it… ♪
[in English] Dance Machine, DM,
Hwang Hyun-woo, officially.
The choreo? Leave that to me.
-[vocalizing]
-[Hyun-woo] Dancing Hyun-woo!
-[Do-mi] Singing Do-mi!
-[Sang-gu] Rapping Sang-gu!
[all] Triangle!
[in Korean] ♪ I love you this much
I love you so much it's overflowing ♪
[in English] ♪ Say T-T-T-Triangle
Say T-T-T-Triangle ♪
EARLY IN THE MORNING
I CHEER FOR YOUR EVERY MOMENT
Just play the backing track.
Seriously, let them do the song.
The most important thing
is getting the Expo line in at the end.
The Ministry of Culture, Sports
and Tourism was adamant about that.
If we don't do it, we're screwed.
Why? Why? Why me?
-[upbeat music playing]
-[gasps]
[in Korean] ♪ My name is Gu Sang-gu
Say it forward, Gu Sang-gu ♪
♪ Say it backward, Gu Sang-gu
Machine Gun Rapper, Gu Sang-gu ♪
♪ My name is Gu Sang-gu
Our Gu Sang-gu ♪
♪ Rap is my everything
Rap is my everything ♪
♪ I wanted to rap
But reality was a cesspool ♪
♪ Rap is my everything
Rap is my everything ♪
♪ I wanted to rap
But reality was a cesspool ♪
♪ Yo, check it
Everybody, come on! ♪
♪ My mom and dad
This is my everything ♪
♪ Everyone laughs at me
Saying I can't rap ♪
♪ I wrote this to show them ♪
♪ And I put my life on the line
To stand on this stage ♪
♪ Gu Sang-gu, my rap is a violent storm ♪
♪ Gu Sang-gu, spinning kick
Tae kwon do dance ♪
♪ Gu Sang-gu, drive it in
Fireball shoot ♪
♪ Gu Sang-gu, throw it hard, fastball ♪
♪ The day that I met you
Was the luckiest one of my life ♪
♪ That's obvious when I look back
Upon it now ♪
♪ The more I get to know you
The more scared I become ♪
It's you! Hey, Byeon Do-mi!
It's me, Hwang Hyun-woo.
♪ How much of it did you ever
Really mean? ♪
♪ Well hey, should I do this
Should I do that? ♪
♪ It's clear that's
What is going through your head, uh ♪
♪ Will you just stop and answer me? ♪
♪ I want to know right now
But the time's not right ♪
♪ You shouldn't do that
You shouldn't do this ♪
-♪ Why is it so complicated, baby ♪
♪ Love is, why is it, why is it
So hard? ♪
♪ Even though every day, every day
You still make me laugh and cry ♪
♪ That it will last forever
That it will go on ♪
♪ Promise me, my love
Oh, my love ♪
-♪ Smile at me… ♪
-[in English] Hey, that's nice.
That's really good there.
[assistant] Sir, are you okay?
Are you okay? Sir!
Not only are they good natured,
they're talented, too.
Way to go…
Tambourine.
[grunts] ♪ Check it out now ♪
Yo!
[in Korean] ♪ Go Sang-gu
I somehow got a feeling, yes I ♪
♪ Do whatever you want
Nobody can't stop me ♪
♪ Don't stop, stop, stop
We're going nonstop ♪
♪ Come into my, come into my
Come into my, my, my, heart ♪
♪ Well hey, should I do this
Should I do that? ♪
♪ It's clear that's
What is going through your head, uh ♪
♪ Will you just stop and answer me? ♪
♪ I want to know right now
But the time's not right ♪
♪ You shouldn't do that
You shouldn't do this ♪
-♪ Why is it so complicated, baby ♪
♪ Love is, why is it, why is it
So hard? ♪
♪ Even though every day, every day
You still make me laugh and cry ♪
♪ That it will last forever
That it will go on ♪
♪ Promise me, my love ♪
-♪ That's how much ♪
-[vocalizes]
[in English]
Yo, everybody put your hands up!
[in Korean] ♪ My mom and dad
This is my everything ♪
♪ Everyone laughs at me
Saying I can't rap ♪
♪ I wanted to show them, success ♪
♪ And I put my life on the line
To stand on this stage ♪
-[Do-mi vocalizes]
-♪ Gu Sang-gu, my rap is a violent storm ♪
♪ Gu Sang-gu, spinning kick
Tae kwon do dance ♪
♪ Gu Sang-gu, drive it in
Fireball shoot ♪
♪ Gu Sang-gu, throw it hard, fastball ♪
[audience cheers]
[in English] He just keeps on going.
[panting]
[audience cheering]
Oh, I think I set a record today.
Looks like I've underestimated you.
Well done.
I did it all.
Whoo!
[audience chanting]
Dancing Machine Hwang Hyun-woo!
-Endless Charm Byeon Do-mi!
-I'm hearing things.
[audience]
Machine Gun Rapper Gu Sang-gu!
-I might need to go to the hospital.
-[gasping]
Do you see that?
[audience]
Dancing Machine Hwang Hyun-woo!
Endless Charm Byeon Do-mi!
Machine Gun Rapper Gu Sang-gu!
TOGETHER, WE ARE WHOLE
ONCE AGAIN, TRIANGLE
I LOVE YOU HWANG HYUN-WOO
BYEON DO-MI ROCKS
SANG-GU IS CRAZY PRETTY
Is there something we forgot?
Hey, hold on.
The Expo, the Expo!
You gotta mention the Expo,
you stupid idiots!
The-The Olympics bid, we…
-Ah!
-Okay, okay.
One, two, three.
Triangle sincerely supports
Gangwon's bid to host the Olympics!
Whoo!
What the hell? This is an outrage!
Goddamn it!
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
-Hey.
Why am I the one supporting you?
-We'll call you for any future gigs.
-Don't ever contact me again.
-Please contact me. Okay?
-Okay. Thank you.
Is that Mr. Park Yong-gu?
Oh!
I love your look. You'll do well overseas.
Here's my card.
What songs did you sing today?
There isn't a singer I don't know.
-Oh, this is…
-You know me?
You should.
I know you.
I am the singer.
Doesn't my outfit
clearly give it away? Huh?
You cried, didn't you? Are you happy?
[mother-in-law]
What a disgrace to the family!
Get over here right this minute!
Did you hear me?
-Huh?
-[sighs]
[Hyun-woo] Hey, Byeon Do-mi.
Don't go.
Let's keep performing together.
Are you happy living like that?
You should be on stage,
where you belong.
You don't plan
to live like that forever, do you?
What on earth are you waiting for?
Get over here right now.
-Hey lady, just give us a minute.
-"Lady"?
What's happening?
Oh, I'm think I'm losing my mind.
[Hyun-woo]
Hey, we can make a lot of money again.
This is the golden age of K-pop.
It's better to be a singer
than an heiress, these days.
Yeah, but, hyung,
her in-laws are super rich, I think.
Oh, come on,
how rich could they possibly be, you know?
Some no-name construction company.
Net worth 1.3 trillion.
What?
Listen to me, damn it! Get over here!
Hello, Mother, one second, okay?
Trust me. Pretty soon,
-I'll get all that money.
-I'm not kidding!
Oh, I swear, I'm going to lose it.
-Man, Do-mi's epic.
-[Do-mi] Oh, I'm sorry.
-Who do you think you are?
-[Do-mi] Oh, well, you see…
What? "Well, you see"?
Do you think I'm your friend?
Are you out of your mind?
Have you gone mad?
This is absolutely unbelievable!
I don't think we'll see her again.
It was nice to be on stage again,
wasn't it?
Yeah, it was. Seriously.
Should we keep doing it?
The two of us?
ONNURI CULTURAL FESTIVAL
TOGETHER WITH THE LOCALS
[in Korean] ♪ Well hey, should I do this?
Should I do that? ♪
♪ It's clear that's
What is going through your head, uh ♪
♪ Will you just stop and answer me? ♪
♪ I want to know right now
But the time's not right ♪
-♪ Yeah ♪
-♪ Yo, everybody put your hands up ♪
♪ My mom and dad
This is my everything… ♪
[upbeat pop music playing]
[photographer in English] A little more.
Good. Yeah, that's good.
-[camera shutter clicking]
-Love that.
Okay, give me more intensity.
Oh, nice. Smoking!
Let's try a sexy look. Sexy. Nice! Oh!
I think we've got enough.
Can we stop now?
Miss Byeon.
Hey, you bastards, do as you're told!
You've got half a year to turn a profit,
or you're disbanding!
Got it?
[all] Yes, Miss Byeon!
-Okay, let's keep going.
-[Hyun-woo] Okay.
New Triangle pose. Okay.
One, two, three!
One more time!
[pop music continues]
[hip-hop music playing]
Are you ready?
♪ Everybody ♪
♪ Everybody, body ♪
♪ Come on now ♪
♪ Come on now
Let me hear you say ♪
♪ What's up
Say T-T-T-Triangle ♪
♪ Say T-T-T-Triangle ♪
[in Korean] ♪ The day that I met you
Was the luckiest one of my life ♪
♪ That's obvious
When I look back upon it now ♪
♪ The more I get to know you
The more scared I become ♪
♪ How much of it did you
Ever really mean? ♪
♪ Well hey, should I do this?
Should I do that? ♪
♪ It's clear that's
What is going through your head, uh ♪
♪ Will you just stop and answer me? ♪
♪ I want to know right now
But the time's not right ♪
♪ You shouldn't do that
You shouldn't do this ♪
-♪ Why is it so complicated, baby ♪
♪ Love is, why is it, why is it
So hard? ♪
♪ Even though every day, every day
You still make me laugh and cry ♪
♪ That it will last forever
That it will go on ♪
♪ Promise me, my love
Oh, my love ♪
♪ Smile at me
With a face full of confidence ♪
♪ Call out to me
With your angelic voice ♪
♪ I love you this much
I love you so much it's overflowing ♪
♪ That's how much ♪
♪ All my people, say ho! ♪
♪ Put your hands up in the air, yo! ♪
♪ Say hey, ho, hey, ho ♪
♪ What is love? Love is
What even is love? Love is ♪
♪ Well, hey, should I do this?
Should I do that? ♪
♪ It's clear that's
What is going through your head, uh ♪
♪ Will you just stop and answer me? ♪
♪ I want to know right now
But the time's not right ♪
♪ You shouldn't do that
You shouldn't do this ♪
-♪ Why is it so complicated, baby ♪
♪ Love is, why is it, why is it
So hard? ♪
♪ Even though every day, every day
You still make me laugh and cry ♪
♪ That it will last forever
That it will go on ♪
♪ Promise me, my love
Oh, my love ♪
♪ Smile at me
With a face full of confidence ♪
♪ Call out to me
With your angelic voice ♪
♪ I love you this much
I love you so much it's overflowing ♪
♪ That's how much ♪
[vocalizing]
[in English] ♪ Triangle's in the house
Triangle's in the house ♪
[song ends]
["Love Is" playing]
♪ Shout it out ♪
♪ Shout it out, shout it out ♪
♪ Our ship is being poisoned
By our greed ♪
♪ Trash piling up
From reckless overconsumption ♪
♪ The selective comfort of those
Who live only for today ♪
♪It's destroying you and me
All of us here ♪
♪ One, two, three, four, my peace ♪
♪ Hang it up, hang it up, now ♪
♪ The world I created ♪
♪ Is coming back to get me ♪
♪ Living for today is ♪
♪ My promise to protect it ♪
♪ Can you hear me? ♪
♪ Nothing lasts forever ♪
♪ Don't run from the uncomfortable truth ♪
♪ Can you hear me? ♪
♪ Shout it out ♪
♪ Shout it out, shout it out ♪
[song ends]